♪♪～
((日輪:おじちゃん
お日様は どんな人の上にも➡
Mister, the sun shines above every person.
同じに輝くんだよ｡
みんなに
光を当ててくれるんだよ))
It gives light to everyone.
Why must you hate me, as well?
(鳳仙)
なぜ お前さえもﾜｼを嫌う…｡
((日輪:
おじちゃんの上にも きっと…➡
It shines above you, too...
きっと冷たくなった
おじちゃんの心を温めてくれる))
I'm sure it'll warm your chilled heart...
なぜ お前さえﾜｼを拒む｡
Why must you reject me, as well?
((日輪:だから おじちゃん
お日様を嫌いにならないでね))
So, Mister,
don't hate the sun.
Why...  When I desire you so...
(鳳仙)なぜ こんなにも
焦がれているのに…｡
I am drying up...
ﾜｼは 渇いていく｡
I can see nothing at all...
見えぬ もう何も…｡
A true night, where no light can reach...
《いかなる光も届かぬ真の夜｡
死してなお➡
So, even in death, the King of the Night must walk into the night...
夜をゆくが夜王の運命か…｡
こ… この光は…》
This is...
This light is...
♪♪～
ひ… 日輪…｡
Hi-Hinowa...
["The Taste of Drinking Under Broad Daylight Is Something Special"]
(日輪)やっと 見せてあげられた｡
I'm finally able to show you...
ずっと 見せてあげたかった…｡
I've always wanted to show you this...
この空を… あなたに…｡
Show you this sky...
言ったでしょう
きっとお日様と➡
Didn't I tell you?
I'd help you make up with the sun.
仲直りをさせてあげるって｡
私 知ってたのよ ずっと｡
I always knew...
どんなに えばりくさったって
どんな ひどいことしたって➡
No matter how arrogant you may be...
No matter how cruel you may be...
あなたは夜王なんて➡
You're not the great King of the Night you claimed to be.
大層なもの
じゃないってことくらい｡
This is all you ever wanted, isn't it?
あなたは ただ
こうしたかったのよね｡
こうして 日向で
居眠りしたかっただけの➡
...A simple old man who just wanted to sleep under the sun.
普通の おじいちゃんなのよね｡
ただ それだけなのに➡
That was all you wanted,
yet you built this foolish city,
なのに こんな
ﾊﾞｶげた街まで作って➡
みんなを敵に回して…｡
turning everyone against you...
ﾊﾞｶな人…｡
What a foolish man...
本当に…｡
Really...
♪♪～
ﾊﾞｶな人…｡
What a foolish man.
♪♪～
(拍手)
(神威)よっ お見事｡
実に鮮やかなお手前｡
Hey!
Bravo!
A truly brilliant performance!!
とは 言いがたいなりだが
いやはや 恐れ入ったよ｡
Well, not really...
but I'm truly amazed.
(神威)
小さき火が 集いに集って➡
Little flames gathered together
ついに 夜王の鎖を焼ききり➡
and finally burned through the chains of the King of the Night,
吉原を照らす
太陽にまでなったか｡
becoming a sun to shine over Yoshiwara, huh?
まさか 本当に
あの夜王を倒しちゃうなんて｡
I never expected you to actually defeat the King of the Night.
遠くまできた
甲斐があったなぁ｡
The long trip was worth it.
久しぶりに おもしろいものを
見せてもらったよ｡
It's been a while since I witnessed something this entertaining.
(神威)
だけど こんなことしたって➡
But I doubt this will be enough to change Yoshiwara.
吉原は
何も変わらないと思うよ｡
吉原に降りかかる闇は
夜王だけじゃない｡
The King of the Night was not the only darkness covering Yoshiwara.
(神威)ｵﾚたち春雨に
幕府中央暗部｡
There's us, Harusame,
and the Bakufu Central Covert Ops.
闇は 限りなく濃い｡
Darkness can be found everywhere.
また 第２ 第３の夜王が
すぐに 生まれることだろう｡
A second or third King of the Night will be born soon enough.
その闇をすべて
払えるとでも思っているのかい？
Do you think you can eliminate all of the darkness?
本当に この吉原を
変えられると思っているのかい？
Do you truly believe that you can change Yoshiwara?
(銀時)変わるさ｡
It'll change.
人が変わりゃ 街も変わる｡
A town changes when its people change.
これから お天道さんも
機嫌を損ねて➡
There may be days when the sun doesn't feel like peeking out from behind the clouds,
雲から ﾂﾗ出さなくなっちまう日も
あるだろうが｡
ｺｲﾂらの光は
もう消えねえよ｡
but their light will never fade again.
そうかい｡
たいした自信だね｡
Really?
You sound pretty confident.
じゃあ さっそく
この第２の夜王と開戦と…｡
How about fighting with the second King of the Night right now?
Kamui!
(神楽)神威!!
I'm your opponent!
(神楽)
お前の相手は 私ｱﾙ!!
I'll fix that twisted attitude of yours!
そのねじ曲がった根性
私が 叩き直して…！
You can't, Kagura-chan!
(新八)ﾀﾞﾒだって 神楽ちゃん！
その体じゃ ﾑﾘだ！
Not in your current condition!
Let me go, stupid four-eyes!
(神楽)離すｱﾙ！ ﾀﾞﾒｶﾞﾈ！
(神威)ｺｲﾂは驚いた｡
Stop it, Kagura-chan!
This is surprising.
まだ 生きてたんだ｡
少しは 丈夫になったらしいね｡
You're still alive?
It appears that you've gotten a little tougher.
(神威)出来の悪い妹だけど
よろしく頼むよ｡
She's not much of a sister, but do take good care of her.
せいぜい
強くしてやってよ｡
Make her stronger, will ya?
(神威)あとｷﾐも
もっと修行しておいてよね｡
Oh, and you should do some more training too.
おい お前！
Hey, you!
(神威)好物のおかずは
とっておいて➡
I'm the kind of person who saves his favorite part of a meal for the end.
最後に食べるﾀｲﾌﾟなんだ｡
(神威)つまり 気に入ったんだよ
ｷﾐが｡
In other words, I've taken a liking to you.
ちゃんと
ｹｶﾞ治しておいてね｡
Make sure to heal those wounds.
まぁ いろいろあると思うけど
死んじゃﾀﾞﾒだよ｡
Well, you probably have a lot to deal with, but don't die.
ｵﾚに殺されるまで｡
...Until I kill you.
(神威)
じゃあね お侍さん｡
See ya, Mr. Samurai.
待て 神威！
Wait, Kamui!
Kamui!
(神楽)神威!!
(阿伏兎)たまげたねぇ｡
吉原に日が昇ってやがる｡
Well, I'll be damned.
The sun has risen above Yoshiwara.
あれが昇ってるってこたぁ
沈んだのは 夜王ってわけかい｡
If that's risen up there, then the King of the Night has sunk below?
(神威)さぁね｡
Who knows.
負けたﾔﾂに
興味はないよ｡
I have no interest in someone who's lost,
(神威)阿伏兎｡
(阿伏兎)ｺｲﾂは 手厳しいや…｡
...Abuto.
Aren't you so critical.
これでも がんばったほうだろ？
I worked my butt off, you know?
なんせ相手は あの夜王を
倒しちまうほどのお嬢さんだ｡
After all, I was against a young lady capable of beating the King of the Night.
(阿伏兎)なぁ お兄さんよ｡
Right, Big Brother?
(神威)阿伏兎｡
また 悪いｸｾが出たね｡
Abuto, you've fallen into your bad habit again.
ｵﾚと
やりあったときもそうだった｡
You were like this when you fought me as well.
同胞を大切にするのは
結構だが➡
I don't mind you treasuring your kind,
加減したまま
力を出しきらず 負けるなんて➡
but losing a fight while holding back your true strength is a disgrace to the Yato.
夜兎の風上にも
おけやしないよ｡
(神威)お前は
夜兎の血を愛でるあまり➡
Your love for the Yato blood has lead you to behave in a way shameful to the Yato.
最も 血に
恥ずべき行為を行ったんだ｡
言っただろう
弱いﾔﾂに用はないって｡
Like I said.
I have no interest in the weak.
ｵﾚは 加減なんてした覚えは
ないがね｡
I don't recall holding myself back.
(阿伏兎)だが あの逸材を
こんなところで消すのは➡
Though I can't deny feeling that it would be a waste to end such talent in a place like this.
もったいないと思ったのも
事実だよ｡
ｱﾝﾀと会ったときと
同じ感覚だった 団長｡
It was the same way I felt when I met you, captain.
実に おもしろい兄妹だよ｡
You siblings fascinate me.
(阿伏兎)嬉しいねぇ｡
有望な新人が続々と｡
I'm very happy.
Promising youngsters coming one after another.
ｵﾚたちの未来は
明るいぜ｡
We've got a bright future ahead of us.
これからは
お前たちの時代だ｡
This is your era now.
ｵﾚたち 古い兎は
夜王とともに…➡
Us old bunnies will be returning to the moon with the King of the Night.
[This is a reference to the Japanese myth of rabbits living on the moon pounding mochi.]
月に還るとするか…｡
(阿伏兎)ありゃあ…
どういう風の吹き回しだ？
Say?
What's going on here?
(神威)阿伏兎…
ｵﾚも お前と同じだ｡
Abuto.
I felt the same way you did.
先が 気になって
１人 やれなかった男がいる｡
I became curious of a man's future and couldn't kill him.
(神威)真の強者とは➡
A man who is truly strong is strong in both body and soul.
強き肉体と 強き魂を
兼ね備えた者…｡
(神威)そんな者とは 程遠い…➡
This man was far from that.
もろい肉体と くだらない
しがらみに とらわれる➡
He had a fragile body and a weak soul bound by worthless beliefs.
脆弱な精神を もつ男だ｡
(神威)だが それでも
あの男は 夜王に勝った｡
Yet that man was able to defeat the King of the Night.
何度 潰されても 立ち上がり➡
Standing every time he was crushed...
Overcoming impossible odds...
圧倒的実力差を覆し➡
最後に 戦場に生き残った…｡
And in the end, he survived on the battlefield.
(神威)おもしろいだろう？
Interesting, isn't it?
The universe sure is a big place.
やっぱり 宇宙は広いね～｡
It's still too early for us to call ourselves the strongest.
ｵﾚたちが 最強を称するのは
まだまだ 早かった…｡
まだ 宇宙には いたんだよ｡
There were still people in this universe
ｵﾚたちとは まったく
別の形の強さをもった連中が…｡
who possessed a totally different form of strength.
侍という…
夜兎に 匹敵する力をもつ修羅…｡
The samurai, with a sense of carnage that can rival the Yato.
ﾜｸﾜｸするじゃないか｡
I can't help but get excited.
あの獲物は ｵﾚのものだよ…｡
He's MY prey.
誰にも 手出しは させない！
I won't let anyone else touch him.
(神威)吉原の変を知れば
うえは 黙っちゃいない｡
Our superiors won't keep quiet once they find out about the changes in Yoshiwara.
そうなれば あの男たちも
ただでは すまないだろう｡
Which means those guys won't get away easily.
ｵﾚは 世渡りが苦手なんだ｡
I'm not very good at negotiating my way through this world.
阿伏兎… お前には まだ
生きていてもらわないと困る｡
Abuto, I still need you to stay alive.
(阿伏兎)つまり うえを黙らせ➡
So come up with a way to keep our superiors and let the samurai live?
侍どもを
死なせぬ手を 考えろと…？
(阿伏兎)おいおい…
冗談 よせよ…｡
Hey, you gotta be kidding me.
なんで ｵﾚが 同族でもない
こんな 辺境の星の蛮族のために➡
Why do I have to work so hard for the sake of some barbarian
そこまでしなきゃ ならねえんだ？
on this remote planet who isn't one of us?
(神威)だって
阿伏兎 言ってただろ？
Because you're the one who said
宇宙の 海賊王への道を
切り開いてくれるって…｡
that you would open the way to becoming the Pirate King of the universe.
(阿伏兎)それと これとは
別だろう！
That's different.
(阿伏兎)おい！ 聞いてんのか!?
Hey, are you listening?
Hey, you bonehead!
(阿伏兎)おい！
すっとこどっこい！
((鳳仙:神威…➡
Kamui, you will eventually learn.
お前も いずれ知ろう…｡
When you're old and look back at the path you took,
年老い…
己が来た道を 振り返ったとき…➡
我らの道には 何もない))
you'll find that our path is empty.
《神威:旦那…
ｵﾚは それで結構だ｡
Boss, that's fine with me.
欲しいものなど ない｡
There isn't anything I want.
振り返ることなど ない｡
There isn't any reason for me to look back.
前しか 見えない…｡
I only see what's ahead.
眼前に広がる 新たな戦場…➡
A new battlefield spreading before my eyes...
That is what I seek.
それこそが ｵﾚの求めしもの…｡
誰よりも 強くなるため行く｡
I strive to become stronger than any other person.
何よりも 強くなるため進む…｡
I move forward to become stronger than anything.
たとえ そこに…
護るものなど 何も なくとも！》
Even if I have nothing left to protect when I get there.
(星海坊主)また えらく➡
You've found an unbearably hot place to rest.
暑苦しい所に
眠らされたもんだな…｡
(星海坊主)ざまあみやがれ
鳳仙よ…｡
Serves you right, Hosen.
遊女たちがよ…➡
The prostitutes...
あの世じゃ
日 浴びさせてやろうってな｡
They wanted to let him sunbathe in the afterlife.
で？ 何の用だよ？
So? What do you want?
ﾀﾞﾁ公だったか…｡
Was he a pal of yours?
Sorry about that.
悪いこと しちまったな…｡
(星海坊主)いや…➡
No, it's just that the more annoying they are...
むかつくﾔﾂほど
いなくなるとな…｡
お前の 墓参りにも
行くことに なりそうだ…｡
So maybe I'll be attending your funeral as well.
よかったな…｡
いや ｵﾚのほうが行くわ｡
Aren't you happy?
No, I'll be attending yours.
通い詰めるわ｡
いや さらに ｵﾚは➡
And making frequent visits.
No, I can top that.
それを 上回っていく｡
ｼﾞｪｯﾄ機で 駆けつける｡
I'll use a jet to visit you.
いいや！
ｵﾚの ｼﾞｪｯﾄ機のほうが早い｡
No. My jet is faster.
いいや！
ｵﾚのｼﾞｪｯﾄ機のほうが ﾁｹｯﾄが安い！
No, my jet has cheaper flights.
(波の音)
相変わらず
派手にやってるらしいな？
It seems you're as crazy as ever.
まさか
あの鳳仙をやっちまうなんざ…➡
I didn't expect you to take down Hosen.
次は
この星海坊主様とやってみるか？
Want to try me, the Umi Bozu, next?
冗談じゃねえ｡
That's not funny.
We just ganged up on him.
あんなもん ただの袋叩きだ｡
１人じゃ どうにもならなかった｡
I had no chance on my own.
お前は そう思っていても…➡
That's what you think,
ｵﾚのｶﾞｷは
そうは思っていないようだ｡
but my kid apparently doesn't agree.
ﾔﾂめ 鳳仙は 自分が殺した
と のたまっているらしい｡
He's saying that he was the one who killed Hosen.
鳳仙の死は 吉原査定の結果
自分が下した処置だと｡
That Hosen's death was a result of the investigation into Yoshiwara.
春雨は 強大すぎる
鳳仙の力をうとんでいた｡
Harusame shunned Hosen's excessive power.
鳳仙を始末した功で
ﾔﾂは 吉原の全権を任せられた｡
The credit for the disposal of Hosen gives him total control over Yoshiwara.
だが ﾔﾂは 吉原に
何も手を出そうとはしなかった｡
But he didn't do anything to Yoshiwara.
手を出すどころか 人員もよこさず
…まったくの手放し状態｡
Not only that, he didn't send any people either.
He's leaving it completely alone.
そうさ…
ﾔﾂは 吉原などに興味はない｡
That's right.
He has no interest in Yoshiwara.
ﾔﾂが興味があるのは…➡
His interest...
お前だ｡
is in you.
よけいな連中が
お前たちに手を出せぬよう➡
He obtained Yoshiwara so other people wouldn't lay a hand on you all.
吉原を手に入れた｡
結果 吉原は救われたが➡
In the end, Yoshiwara was saved, but...
お前… 殺されるぞ｡
you'll be killed.
That so?
そうかい？ 今度会ったら
助かったと言っといてくれ｡
Tell him thanks if you ever see him.
神楽は
ﾔﾂを救いたいと思っている｡
Kagura wants to save him.
Despite all the badmouthing she does,
憎まれ口を叩いても…➡
ﾔﾂが 以前のような兄に
戻ることを望んでいる｡
she wishes for her brother to go back to how he used to be.
お前が ﾔﾂと
対峙するときがきても… きっと｡
Even if the two of you end up facing off, I'm sure...
…お前ならどうする？
What would you do?
神楽の前で
ﾔﾂに命を狙われたとき➡
If he comes after your life in Kagura's presence,
お前なら… どうする？
what would you do?
Earthlings are an odd bunch.
地球人ってのは 妙な連中だ｡
憎んだ相手の墓まで作る｡
They make a grave for someone they hated.
憎しみがあっても
そこに 同じだけ愛情もある｡
Where there is hate, there is also love.
ｵﾚたちは ﾀﾞﾒだ｡
愛情があったとしても➡
We're no good.
Even if there was love,
一度憎めば すべて黒く染まる｡
once there is hate, everything turns black.
あのとき ｵﾚは 黒く染まった｡
Back then, I turned black.
そして ﾔﾂのすべてを
黒く塗りつぶしてしまった｡
And I smeared everything in him with black.
もしかしたら お前なら…➡
Maybe you could find a different solution.
ｵﾚと違う答えが…｡
ちと しゃべりすぎたか…｡
忠告はしたぞ｡ 親の責任として｡
I've spoken too much.
I've warned you.
As a parent's duty...
じゃあな｡
See ya.
死ぬんじゃねえぞ｡
Don't die.
Isn't that great?
よかったじゃないすか！
結果ｵｰﾗｲですよ！ ｱｯﾊｯﾊﾊﾊ…！
It all worked out in the end.
In any case, Yoshiwara is a peaceful place now.
とにもかくにも こうして
吉原に平和が訪れたんだ｡
ｳｺﾞｰｯ!!
何がｵｰﾗｲだ この野郎!!
What the hell worked out, moron?!
その気になれば
ﾔﾂら いつだって この街➡
Those bastards could do whatever they want with this town if they felt like it!
どうにかできるってことｱﾙよ！
そもそも
なんでﾔﾂは 私たちを…➡
And why are they letting us flounder around here?!
泳がせて
おくようなﾏﾈしてるｱﾙか！
私たちを おちょくってるｱﾙか！
ﾑｷｰｯ!!
Are they toying with us?!
I'm pissed!
心配いらねえよ｡
Don't worry.
As long as I'm alive, he won't touch this place.
ｵﾚが生きてるかぎり
ﾔﾂは ここには手を出さねえ｡
は？ それ どういうことですか？
What's that supposed to mean?
まっ そういうことだ｡
いや 全然わかんないんですけど｡
Well, there you have it.
Yeah, I have no idea what you're talking about.
わからなくていいんだ｡
とにかく 大丈夫ってことだ｡
You don't need to.
At any rate, it's fine.
しかし つくづく
難儀な連中だねぇ｡
But these people really like to suffer, huh?
さっさと こんな面倒な街捨てて
地上で生活すりゃいいものを｡
They should just abandon this town and live on the surface.
(月詠)この街の遊女たちは皆➡
All of the prostitutes here were sold when they were innocent children.
分別も利かぬ幼き頃に
売られた者ばかり｡
地上で生きていくにも➡
They have no idea how to survive on the surface.
どうやって生きていけばいいか
わからない者➡
Many do not even understand the meaning of freedom.
自由の意味さえ知らぬ者も
たくさんいる｡
Hinowa stayed because she couldn't abandon those women.
そんな遊女たちを
捨て置けないと➡
日輪が残ったんじゃ｡
私たちで
新しい吉原を作っていこうと｡
We intend to build a new Yoshiwara...
A wonderful town we could show to our children without shame.
私たちの子供に見せても
恥ずかしくない➡
立派な街を作ろうと｡
で どのへんが変わったんですか？
So...
What's exactly changed?
The red-light district's gone, while there's been an increase in  mas**** parlors and s***lands.
(月詠)遊郭がなくなって
｢ﾍ…ｿ…｣などが増えた｡
And caba*** clubs and gro**** pubs are quite popular. Yep.
あとｷｬﾊﾞｸﾗ
｢お…ﾊﾟﾌﾞ｣なども人気だなぁ うん｡
Nothing's changed at all!
全然 変わってねえだろうが！
全然 子供に恥ずかしいだろうが!!
How can you show this to children without being ashamed?!
You could never explain what this stuff is!
何？ って聞かれても
答えられねえよ！
まぁまぁ…
今までは強制されてたのが➡
Now, now, now, now.
The problem was that they were being forced to do these things.
問題だったわけだから➡
Now, they can make their own choices.
今は選択の自由が
あるわけでしょ？
着物だけじゃない
ﾅｰｽにﾐﾆｽｶﾎﾟﾘｽとか いろいろ｡
No longer limited to kimonos.
There are nurse outfits and miniskirt police uniforms and...
That's a freedom for you!
それ
ｱﾝﾀが自由になってるだけだろ！
No no, the chains have been shattered.
いや
もう鎖は解かれたわけだから➡
They've been released from their chains.
みんな
もう呪縛は解かれたわけだから｡
Come on!
ほら 早くおし このﾌﾞﾀ野郎！
ﾜﾝ！
Hurry it up, you pig!
Woof!
Why is a pig barking?!
なんで ﾌﾞﾀがﾜﾝとか言ってんだよ｡
ﾜﾝ！
殺すよ！
I'll kill you!
Woof!
おい～ 思いっきり
鎖に つながれてる人いるよ！
Hey!
We've got a person in chains right here!
自分から呪縛されてる人 いるよ！
Somebody's choosing to be chained up right here!
ちょっと！
これ晴太君 大丈夫なんですか？
Hey!
Is Seita-kun really okay here?!
ちゃんと まっとうな生活
送れてるんでしょうね!?
He's living a normal life, right?!
あぁ 晴太なら大丈夫じゃ｡
Yeah. Seita's fine.
日輪とともに寝泊まりし➡
He's staying with Hinowa and working at a toy store.
ｵﾓﾁｬ屋でﾊﾞｲﾄしておる｡
はぁ よかった｡
Whew... That's a relief.
At least there's a store for kids around here.
子供らしいお店もあって｡
That's just an XXX store?!
[Adult Toy Store]
って ただのﾓｻﾞｲｸ屋じゃねえか！
Sorry, I'd already expected something like this when I heard the words "toy store."
悪いけど今
ｵﾓﾁｬ屋って言われた時点で➡
予想ついてたから｡
くるなって思ってたから！
I totally saw this coming, you know?!
そうか｡ 次はがんばるとしよう｡
I see.
I'll work harder on the next one.
がんばらなくて いいんだよ｡
ﾎﾞｹてんの？ ﾅﾒてんの!?
You don't have to!
Are you playing dumb?!
Are you making fun of me?!
(晴太)
銀さん！ みんな 久しぶり～!!
Gin-san! Everyone!
Long time no see!
お前は ﾓﾋﾞﾙｽｰﾂみてえな音出して
近づいてくんじゃねえ！
You! Stop running towards us sounding like a mobile suit!
I've missed you, everyone!
会いたかったんだよ みんな！
ｵｲﾗ この街でがんばって…｡
I'm going to work hard in this town...
What's the big idea, brat?!
おのれは
何してくれてけつかんねん！
Tsukuyo-san, help!
月詠さん ﾍﾙﾌﾟ！ 事件発生です!!
We've got a problem!
ｷﾞｬ～！ どこ狙ってんだぁ！
Gah! Where're you aiming at?!
Outta the way, four-eyes!
どけ～ ﾒｶﾞﾈ～！
Give me back my first time!
ﾜｼの初めてを返せ ｺﾗ～！
どうだい？ 私たちの街は｡
So what do you think of our town?
It's just like some other town.
どっかの街と そっくりある｡
Yeah.
そうだな ｵﾚたちの街と
何にも変わらねえ｡
It's just like ours.
下品で凶暴で優しくて冷たくて➡
Vulgar and brutal...
Gentle and cold...
笑顔も涙も お天道様もある➡
Smiles and tears...
And you've got the sun.
Just a normal town.
ただの普通の街だ｡
(日輪)ｽﾃｷでしょ｡
Isn't it wonderful?
[Yoshiwara is Burning]
[Fin]
うめえ…｡
...It's great.
[Ask Mr. Ginpachi!!]
Ask Mr. Ginpachi!
Uh...
We have a question from pen name "Off-season Thunderdome."
"When Kagura's older brother Kamui showed up during a flashback in episode 42, a couple years ago,
and also when you could see him from behind in a previous ending sequence, I believe his hair was black.
What is going on here?
Was I just imagining things?"
You weren't.
[Rejected]
Uh...The next one is from pen name "Rectal Punch from Hell."
During the "Yoshiwara Is Burning" arc,
which part of Yoshiwara was burning?
[Rejected]
[The End]
[Preview]
After the end of this long battle,
we had only one thought...
Yes...
We want to become stronger!
The next episode:
"All Adults are Instructors for All Children."
[People who are further along on their quest for strength than Shinpachi and Kagura appear.]
え～ ﾍﾟﾝﾈｰﾑ
狂い咲きｻﾝﾀﾞｰﾄﾞｰﾑさんからの質問｡
[Starting next week, it's back to business as usual at Odd Jobs Gin.]
｢神楽のお兄ちゃんの神威って➡
一昨年の
42話の回想で出てきたときや➡
[See you next time.]
以前のｴﾝﾃﾞｨﾝｸﾞで
後ろ姿が出てきたとき➡
髪の色が
黒かったと思うのですが➡
それって
いったい どういうことですか？
私の気のせいでしょうか？｣
気のせいじゃありません｡
え～
ﾍﾟﾝﾈｰﾑ 直腸地獄拳さんからの質問｡
｢吉原炎上篇って吉原のどの辺が
炎上してたんでしょうか？｣